<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on dvoros.com</title><link>https://dvoros.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on dvoros.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Daniel Voros</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 16:51:25 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dvoros.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Commenting Metapost</title><link>https://dvoros.com/posts/commenting-metapost/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 16:51:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://dvoros.com/posts/commenting-metapost/</guid><description>Okay, okay, not really a metapost as this isn&amp;rsquo;t a post about posts but a post about commenting on this blog.
I wanted to introduce some commenting functionality as some of my posts (like this one!) are meant to help others facing similar issues and having the ability to ask/respond might benefit others.
I&amp;rsquo;m also planning on writing about stuff where I feel like I don&amp;rsquo;t have a good enough solution and would like to get feedback from others.</description></item><item><title>Bikes and Parking Places</title><link>https://dvoros.com/posts/bikes-and-parking-places/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 13:41:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://dvoros.com/posts/bikes-and-parking-places/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of saving years of seemingly useless data and then trying to make sense of it. If I see a (sort-of) publicly available datasource that I can scrape and save I jump on it. It started with bike and moped sharing and later continued with &amp;ldquo;smart parking&amp;rdquo;.
In this post I&amp;rsquo;m going to explain the process of finding, obtaining and archiving these datasets and will follow up with analysis later.</description></item><item><title>Saving endangered YouTube videos</title><link>https://dvoros.com/posts/youtube-backup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 15:17:03 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://dvoros.com/posts/youtube-backup/</guid><description>Remember that video that you thought was funny ten years ago but didn&amp;rsquo;t age well enough to stay on YouTube? I do too and I hate that I can&amp;rsquo;t find it anymore! To avoid this from happening again, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to save my favorites to a playlist and regularly back it up.
I have a short shell script cron&amp;rsquo;d to run every morning on a Scaleway server that saves new additions to Object Storage.</description></item></channel></rss>